You talked about yesterday how you
helped build a culture at St. Diego
State. You have an opportunity to kind
of do that here. Just what was that
experience like and what did you learn
there that you believe can help you
here?
>> Yeah. Um, that experience was great,
man. Just being able to be in that role,
being able to have people follow me. Um,
but it also didn't come easy. I feel
like you kind of got to uh instill your
character into the guys around you. You
can't just run around uh saying certain
things to guys because that's not going
to resonate with people. But once you
really connect with guys on a different
level, then I feel like that that's when
you get some like like you said, like
some cultural changes going.
>> Why was it important for you to finish
your career there at San Diego State
opposed to transferring?
>> Yeah, I feel like um for me personally,
man, I just uh my main goal is to get to
the NFL and I felt like, you know, just
staying there where my feet were
playing. It was, you know, something
that I felt certain of. And, you know, I
didn't want to go somewhere and put a
lot of question marks in the air.
Whereas, if I like it over there, I may
not. I may get along with the coach, I
may not. But um so I just felt like, you
know, staying where my feet were
currently playing was my best option to
get to the league.
>> Guess a lot of lot of the rankings had
you had you lower.
>> A lot of guys that haven't been drafted
yet. You feel you have something to
prove to these people?
>> Yeah, definitely, man. Um at the end of
the day, man, I feel like obviously this
organization views me uh how they uh
view me, and I feel like that that's all
that I really care about. I don't really
care about any of the other media
outlets, but um like you said, it's
definitely like something to prove. Just
uh you know, people that's out there
doubting, but there's always going to
people that doubt you. So, you know,
just I'm always remain hungry
regardless.
>> Chris, we've seen some of the numbers on
you. Four interceptions, two return for
touchdowns. Tell me what you do that
doesn't show up on the stat sheet very
well. Redirecting receivers, hands,
feet. Tell me about some of that stuff
that you do. Uh yeah, I feel like uh
like uh playing corner in general,
there's a lot of things that that get
unnoticed. You know, if the ball doesn't
come to your side, no, nobody really
understands if you was in good coverage
or bad coverage. So, I definitely say uh
just being able to uh you know, stay
focused and locked in during the game
when, you know, the ball may not be
coming my way, understanding that at any
point they can. So, I feel like just
always uh staying in tune to doing my
job and also uh you know, making sure
everybody doing the right things on the
field as well.
>> How much do you know about Miami, the
city? Have you ever been to South
Florida before this? And what are you
excited about of being down here?
>> Yeah. Um, so I actually I I trained like
my pre my pre-drive training down here
in Fort Lauderdale. So I was here for a
few months. Uh, but you know, I'm just
glad to be back, man. I felt like, you
know, coming from California. This
really the the closest thing to it. It's
a little bit more humid out here, but
I'm just excited to get out of
California, man. I've been there my
whole life. I went to school there. Um,
but I feel like I was definitely ready
to branch out and kind of, you know, get
a new beginning, and I'm glad that it's
here. XP where where do you
>> at Boritos?
>> Oh, you were at Boritos. Okay. In Davy.
>> Yes, sir.
>> Okay. Okay.
>> You know you can play um nickel outside
and also even safety if needed. Um is
outside corner your favorite?
>> Yeah, I I'll probably say that that's
where I'm most comfortable at just cuz
you know that's where I've been playing
mainly. But um you know, whatever I got
to do to help the team out and what
whatever uh we can do to uh be the best
fit, I feel like uh you know, I could do
whatever. Chris, what an NFL quarterback
quarterback did you maybe try to model
your game after and why?
>> Um, definitely just all the guys at the
top, man. Like obviously like Pat
Certan. Um, JC Horn's another guy I like
his game and I just like what they do to
the game. JC Horn, he's a real physical
guy and he's also real like savvy in
coverage and understands a lot of a lot
of things. Uh, you know, in zone
coverage, being able to read the
quarterback and understand route
concepts. I feel like that's a part of
my game that I that I take from his. How
do you overcome when there's a big size
differential between you and a receiver?
>> Uh, yeah. I feel like you honestly, you
just got to charge it to the game. Uh,
you know, nobody out there is going to
be the same size. I'm going have to take
on blocks from a t pulling tackle and,
you know, I can't do nothing about it
but do it. There's nothing to complain
about. So, if that's my matchup, that's
my matchup.
>> Chris, they've talked about physicality
and aggression here. I saw last night
that uh Jeff Hafley told you you've got
the right attitude. What is that
attitude and and how will you display
that on the field?
>> Yeah, I feel like my attitude is just to
always be relentless, man, and always
remain hungry. I feel like no matter
what I'm doing, especially in college,
like whether it was uh outside, in the
slot, on special teams, at gun or
whatever it was, like I'm just always
100% uh putting all my effort out there,
being relentless on the field. So, I
definitely just uh bring that to my game
for sure.
>> You going to try to get jersey one from
the veteran or you got a backup plan? Uh
I I'm going probably just go with a
backup plan. U understanding you know
he's been here longer than me and you
know I'm not owed anything. You know
what I mean? So uh you know if the time
comes where I'm able to get into that
when I earn it. Definitely.
>> What are the last uh 12 hours been like
for you? I'm guessing that you're
watching the draft from home back in
California.
>> Yeah. Um crazy man. It's surreal just uh
you know literally like watching my
dreams come true. Being surrounded by my
loved ones, my family, my girl and you
know some of my closest homies. But just
being there with all them in that
moment, seeing my phone ring, man, it
was surreal. Like the whole day I was
trying to be as calm as possible, but as
soon as my phone rang, like my stomach
dropped and you know, just the nerves
and the emotions fell through, man. But
it it's a great feeling. I'm so excited
to be here.
>> Did you have a conviction that you would
be taking in the first round or did you
just
>> um having a draft party because we're
having a draft party?
>> Yeah, I definitely had a feeling, but uh
you know, the the draft could go a
number of ways. So, I'm not gonna say
that I was 100% confident. You know what
I the team could value somebody
differently. So, uh, and I feel like
that's the case why I'm here today.
Obviously, this team value me more than
more than other guys. And, you know,
that's a blessing. So, you know, I I
plan to repay that back here.
>> Value doesn't mean anything more to you,
seeing the team not just take you, but
trade up to go get you.
>> Yeah, for sure. I feel like growing up
watching the draft and stuff, that
always meant a team like really wanted
that guy and that was their guy and they
wanted to make sure that they got him.
So, like you said, that definitely makes
a difference in understanding, you know,
my value here and for sure how the staff
sees me.
>> What has today been like for you as I
imagine you took the first flight out
long travel and then uh what have been
your impressions of this building?
>> Yeah. Um like like you said, I hopped on
a flight at uh at 8:00 this morning. So,
I just got in a little while ago, man.
But it's be it's beautiful, man. I went
on like a quick tour around, but man,
everything just looks so good. I'm just
so excited to, you know, actually start
start being here. Did you meet Kayen
Proctor?
>> I haven't. No, sir.
>> You can't mess.
>> Yeah. Yeah, I know that. Yes, sir.
>> Is your goal to be a rookie starter?
>> Yes, for sure. Um, you know, and uh you
know, whether that happens or not,
that's not going to affect the way I
play. I'm a still like like I said, I'm
a relentless player, so if I got to find
another way to get on the field, I will.
>> When did you start when did you start
thinking that being a first round pick
was a good possibility for you? I mean,
what was it that happened that gave you
that?
>> Um, I honestly I I kind of valued myself
up there a while, but but once I um once
I really thought it was set in stone was
really after like I just kind of put
everything like uh like specifically at
the combine like when I kind of put
those numbers down, I felt like um you
know the teams there was a lot of
question marks about certain parts of my
game and I feel like I answered all
those. So, I felt like there was just no
other questions why why I shouldn't be
in that conversation.
>> The biggest question you think? Uh,
probably my speed for sure.
>> Confidence is a huge part of playing
corner the NFL level. Just how do you
remain confident um if someone catches a
touchdown on you? I know that didn't
really, you know, happen a lot last
year, but just how do you remain
confident um during the ups and downs of
the game?
>> Yeah, for sure. I I I just remember like
like why like my wise and, you know, my
my relentless determination to to be the
best, man. I feel like I I'm an ultra
competitor and I always want to be the
best and you know, part of being the
best is getting to be sometimes. So, um,
like I dealt with that my my career.
Like last year, I didn't give up any
touchdowns, but the year before I did.
And, uh, you know, like you said, that
definitely takes a hitter and
confidence, but at the end of the day,
you got to understand, you know,
everybody gets hit and it's a part of
the game. So, you know, shake back and
make the next play.
>> Chris, the ball production for you last
year took like a big leap from not just
the interceptions, but also the passes,
defense. What were some of the things
that went into that? And, you know, what
what part of that was things that you
worked on versus kind of just the
opportunities that presented themselves
on the field? Yeah, I think uh probably
the biggest part was just my confidence.
My my confidence jumped from my junior
year to my senior year just trusting my
eyes and trusting what I watched on
film. Just being able to play out there
free and not have any any second
thoughts in myself.
>> Did coach Hley sort of explain how your
skill set fits into the style of defense
that he wants to play? How did that how
does that align? Um,
I just feel like uh like we haven't went
in depth on it, but I feel like um
definitely just talking about like my
like my my play style, like how I'm a
how I'm a physical relentless player. Uh
that's definitely uh you know what he
wants his defense to be like.
>> I want to ask you about your ethnicity.
I I think your mother we I was trying to
I watched your draft day.
>> Your mother is she Polynesian?
>> Filipino.
>> Filipino. Yes, sir.
>> Okay. So, you're like half Filipino? I'm
half like half Filipino. Yes, sir.